<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BMI Calculator</string>

    <string name="help_menu">
        You can calculate your BMI using this app. I recommend this app only for <b>adults</b> age starting from 20 years.
        \n\n\nYou can enter your weight and height. You have to select what measurement type you are using.
        \n\t\t\tkg = kilograms\n\t\t\tlb = pounds\n\t\t\tcm = centimeters\n\t\t\tft = feets
        \n\n\nAfter entering your data you can have result by pressing CalculateBMI button.
        In result you will see your BMI value, your health status and the weight you have to maintain according to your height.
        \n\n\nThen you can see BMI chart classified by World Health Organization(W.H.O).
        \n\n\nFinally you can get idea about your health and your nutrition level.
        \n\n\n\nFor more details : <b>sunerasu2216@gmail.com</b>
        \n\n\n\n\nEnjoy App.
        \nThank You!
    </string>

    <string name="why_bmi">
        BMI (Body Mass Index) is important as it is widely regarded that your chances of having a longer and healthier life are improved if you have a healthy BMI.
        \n\nIf your BMI is high, you may also have an increased risk of developing <b>type 2 diabetes</b>, as well as other metabolic diseases such as <b>hypertension, high cholesterol and heart disease.</b>
        \n\n\nBMI helps determine someone\'s overall health risk and what treatment may be appropriate.
        \n\n\nIf your BMI is low, it means you are underweight. If high, it means you are overweight or obese.
        \n\n\nSome risks of underweight
        \n\t\tOsteoporosis
        \n\t\tAnemia
        \n\t\tSlow or impaired growth
        \n\t\tFeeling tired all the time
        \n\t\tGetting sick frequently
        \n\nSome risks of overweight
        \n\t\tHigh blood pressure
        \n\t\tHeart disease
        \n\t\tType 2 diabetes
        \n\t\tOsteoarthritis
        \n\t\tHigh cholesterol and blood lipids(LDL)
        \n\n\nTo know more, visit : <a href="https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/obesity-prevention-source/obesity-definition/obesity-definition-full-story/" target="_blank">Why Use BMI</a>
    </string>

</resources>
